epson.com.ph 2010-06-14

# Privacy Policy

Privacy

 **Privacy Policy**  
Epson Singapore Pte Ltd recognises that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site or sites operated by Epson Singapore Pte Ltd and/or any of its other affiliates. Other Epson branded or co-branded sites may operate under their own privacy policies.

 **Identifying Information**  
In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. Generally, Epson requests identifying information when you:

1\. Register on any of our web site.  
2\. Place an order or request notification of order status.  
3\. Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion.  
4\. Participate in a rebate programme, contest, or other promotional offer.  
5\. Register to receive mailings, such as a product catalog, or e-mail notification such as when a product will become available.  
6\. Register an Epson product.  
7\. Request information or files from technical support or customer service.

In these instances, Epson will ask for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time as described in the Opting-Out section below.

 **What Epson Will Do With Your Information  
** If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by Epson and will only be used by Epson to support your customer relationship with us. For example, we may send you a mailed announcement of product upgrades, special offers, and other new products and services from Epson. We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent, except to vendors which provide services to Epson as described in this policy or where we believe we are obligated to provide it under law such as in response to a summons. Epson may also enhance or merge your information collected on the web site with data from other Epson sources or third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

 **Epson Traffic Analyses**  
Epson may also collect anonymous (non-personal) visitor information such as an IP Address, browser type, pages visited and time spent on the web site. This information is used only by Epson to understand better our site to improve the customer experience, usability and site content. Most anonymous data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. Epson may contract with third party service providers and suppliers to provide these services. These suppliers act on Epson's behalf and are bound to the Epson Privacy Policy contractually to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Epson. They agree with Epson that they may not use any Epson data for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Epson.

These data collection methods will not collect any personal information, such as names, addresses, email addresses, from Site visitors. The data collected does not create or store individual profiles about our visitors. At any time, you may elect to opt out of receiving tracking cookies through the internet options on your browser.

 **  
Opting Out  
** Epson provides several easy means for you to tell us you do not wish to receive e-mails. If you do not want to receive any information about products or services that we feel may be of interest to you, you can simply tell us at the time you give us your personal information by checking the appropriate box. Or, at any other time you can easily opt out of by going into your account and changing your preferences. You will also be able to respond to any e-mail you receive by replying to the "unsubscribe" information included with the mailing. You can also advise us by letter to the address below at any time.

To: The Web Master  
E-Project Department  
No.1 HarbourFront Place,  
#03-02 HarbourFront Tower One,  
Singapore 098633

 **  
What Others May Do With Your Information  
** Epson does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through this Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organisation for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time Epson may use agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for Epson (such as a database management service), however, they are required by us to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services for Epson. In addition, Epson may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our users.

 **Third Party Links  
** The Site does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave the site or sites operated by Epson Singapore Pte Ltd and/or any of its other affiliates, Epson cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site.

 **  
Cookies  
** At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a "cookie". We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. We only use cookies to learn ways to enhance our Site, and to give you better, more personalised service while in the Site, such as saving your preferences for frequently purchased items. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is sent. However, some functions of the Site will not function if you refuse cookies.
